<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ramadan Tips</string>

    <string name="day_text_1">Day 1</string>
    <string name="day_text_2">Day 2</string>
    <string name="day_text_3">Day 3</string>
    <string name="day_text_4">Day 4</string>
    <string name="day_text_5">Day 5</string>
    <string name="day_text_6">Day 6</string>
    <string name="day_text_7">Day 7</string>
    <string name="day_text_8">Day 8</string>
    <string name="day_text_9">Day 9</string>
    <string name="day_text_10">Day 10</string>
    <string name="day_text_11">Day 11</string>
    <string name="day_text_12">Day 12</string>
    <string name="day_text_13">Day 13</string>
    <string name="day_text_14">Day 14</string>
    <string name="day_text_15">Day 15</string>
    <string name="day_text_16">Day 16</string>
    <string name="day_text_17">Day 17</string>
    <string name="day_text_18">Day 18</string>
    <string name="day_text_19">Day 19</string>
    <string name="day_text_20">Day 20</string>
    <string name="day_text_21">Day 21</string>
    <string name="day_text_22">Day 22</string>
    <string name="day_text_23">Day 23</string>
    <string name="day_text_24">Day 24</string>
    <string name="day_text_25">Day 25</string>
    <string name="day_text_26">Day 26</string>
    <string name="day_text_27">Day 27</string>
    <string name="day_text_28">Day 28</string>
    <string name="day_text_29">Day 29</string>
    <string name="day_text_30">Day 30</string>

    <string name="quote_title_1">The Journey Starts Here – Bismillah!</string>
    <string name="quote_description_1">Its finally here…the blessed month of Ramadan!
Todays tips:
• Purify your intention for fasting. Make sure its
purely for Allahs sake.
• Set multiple alarms for as late a suhoor as
possible – not to be missed!
• Book one or two 30-minute slots of Quran
recitation each day (you can add more slots, but these
should be your bare minimum for the day).</string>

    <string name="quote_title_2">Remember Last Ramadan?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_2">How was it? Was it productive, or did you barely
survive?
If you had an unproductive Ramadan last year, dont
repeat it this year. Feeling guilty about last years
Ramadan wont benefit you unless you can use that
guilt to light up a burning desire in you TODAY to do
better this year, improve yourself, and not fall in the
same traps as last year.
On the other hand, if you had a super productive Rama-
dan last year, Alhamdulillah! Try to recall what worked
for you last year and how you can improve on that.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_3">Are You Busy Yet Unproductive?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_3">Whenever we think of ‘unproductive people during
Ramadan, we think of people who waste time staying
up all night watching TV and sleeping the whole day
until Asr (or sometimes right through to Maghrib)!
But theres another type of unproductive person during
Ramadan:
These are the workaholics – those who barely have time
to worship Allah (Subhanahu Wa Taala) during Rama-
dan because they are so busy with life/work/family and
everything else they are involved in. They also give no
time to read the Quran, barely give charity, and
Taraweeh prayer is simply out of the question!
You may argue that this is not too bad - at least they
are ‘productive. But are they? Are they wasting their
Ramadan? In the grand scheme of things, if they died
today, will all their ‘busy-ness benefit them or will it be
a ‘waste?
We need to be careful of this second type of unproduc-
tive behavior. It affects us all, especially those with
busy schedules. Ramadan can easily slip from us due to
our busy lifestyles and well only regret it on the last
day of Ramadan. So lets not regret it this year!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_4">Time For A Daily Review!</string>
    <string name="quote_description_4">Spend the last 10-15 minutes of each day of Ramadan
reviewing your day. (This could be a simple mental
exercise or written down).
If your day was productive, ask yourself what went
right. What were the ingredients that made this day
productive? How can I replicate this experience each
day? Remember to thank Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala for
blessing you with a productive day.
If it was unproductive, ask yourself what went wrong.
How can I avoid such a day repeating itself during
Ramadan? Ask Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala to help you
make your future days productive. Renew your inten-
tion and be positive that, if you are granted life, the
next day will be better.
You want to be constantly developing and improving
each day during Ramadan, so that by the last 10 days
youre at your peak InshaAllah!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_5">Productivity For The Sake Of…?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_5">“Say, "Indeed, my prayer, my rites of sacrifice, my living
and my dying are for Allah, Lord of the worlds” (Surah
Al-Anaam, 6:162).
Therefore, our productivity and efforts should be
directed to Him and to what He is pleased with. Some-
times we just perform actions for the sake of doing
them, without considering the intentions behind them.
Yet we know our actions are judged by the intention.
The next time you embark on any productive activity,
ask yourself, “Is this for Allah (Subhanahu Wa Taala) or
not?”</string>

    <string name="quote_title_6">Whats On Your Mind?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_6">In our day-to-day battle to continuously stay productive
during Ramadan, its easy to become obsessed with
some of the physical productivity issues; how many
hours did I sleep? How many calories did I consume? Did
I exercise?
Even though this is important, remember that physical
productivity is only a means and not the end goal itself.
In our definition as ProductiveMuslims, physical produc-
tivity is about optimizing your physical ability to enable
you to serve Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala better and
worship Him better.
What you should be concerned about is: Will Allah
Subhanahu Wa Taala accept my fast? Did I pray on time
with all the sunnahs? Did I read Quran? Remember,
Ramadan is not about just making it to the iftar table at
the end of the day. Rather it is about attaining a new
level of spirituality with Allah through your actions</string>

    <string name="quote_title_7">When Will You Be Productive?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_7">Today is a final call to all those who are yet to jump on
the bandwagon of being productive for His sake to
come aboard on our journey.
If you do not resolve to become productive this Rama-
dan, then when will you ever be productive? And if
youre already productive, then is your productivity
truly for His sake?
This Ramadan we want to make sure you have a ‘guilt-
free Ramadan with no regrets, so you can take advan-
tage of this opportunity!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_8">Start At Suhoor</string>
    <string name="quote_description_8">When should you start your day during Ramadan?
Should you start early (thus have a longer fast day) or
should you sleep as much as you can until you really
have to wake up?
My advice: your productive day should start right after
suhoor (no, Im not joking!) Try this tonight/tomorrow
and see how you feel:
Sleep as early as you can (ideally after Taraweeh). Then
wake up 1 hour before Fajr and have a healthy suhoor.
Relax after your meal, pray Fajr, read some Quran and
then start your days work. Work on 1 to 3 most impor-
tant tasks of the day; these could be work-related or
family-related. Whatever it is, make sure that:
• Theres nothing more important than these
tasks and
• You get them done and not get distracted
As many a hadith narrate, suhoor is a blessing - so dont
miss it. Start your day with it</string>

    <string name="quote_title_9">Start At Suhoor - Continued</string>
    <string name="quote_description_9">Below are answers to common questions about this
technique:
Q. Whats wrong with sleeping after suhoor?
A. If you ever wondered why your Ramadan days are so
tiring and why youre always tired/moody at
work/school, this may be your answer. Try staying
awake after suhoor for a few days and youll notice the
difference in your attitude and productivity levels.
Q. You mean I shouldnt sleep from suhoor all the way
till night?!
A. Of course not! That would be a killer! What is meant
is that you stay awake for a minimum of 3 hours after
suhoor to pray Fajr, read Quran and get 1-3 important
tasks of your day done. After that youre “allowed” to
sleep or take naps to prep yourself up before
work/school or delay the nap to just before or after
Dhuhr</string>

    <string name="quote_title_10">Oh No, I Missed My Suhoor!</string>
    <string name="quote_description_10">Here are 6 quick tips if youve missed your suhoor and
want to stay productive:
1. Dont panic: Calm down, pray Fajr, read some
Quran. Youll be fine!
2. Dont obsess over it: Avoid constantly remind-
ing yourself during the day that you missed suhoor,
that you only had one meal last night, etc. Just having
these thoughts is enough to drain your energy and give
you an excuse to be unproductive.
3. Get on with your day: An athlete once said,
“Theres nothing more powerful than a made up mind.”
Make up your mind to be productive, talk to yourself
like an athlete, and get on with your day!
4. Nap if you need to: If you feel super hungry,
then take short naps/breaks to help yourself pull
through the day.
5. Keep yourself busy: Ever had one of those
Ramadan days that went by so quickly? Chances are
you spent that day either super busy or doing some-
thing you really enjoyed. Try to do the same here and
you wont feel that you even missed suhoor at all,
InshaAllah.
6. Make dua to Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala to
help you during the day. Remember the verse “It is You
we worship and You we ask for help” (Al-Fatiha. 1:5). If
were fasting for Him then lets ask Him to help us with
our fasting and to perform it correctly, whether we miss
suhoor or not.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_11">Time For A Pop Quiz!</string>
    <string name="quote_description_11">Being a third of the way through this month, lets
review your progress.
•How many days in the past 10 days have you
managed to wake up for suhoor just before Fajr?
•How many days in the past 10 days have you
managed to stay awake after Fajr and got some impor-
tant work done in the early morning hours?
Give yourself one point for each day you succeeded.
The higher you scored, the greater the sign that youre
having a Productive Ramadan already!
These two ingredients are key to having a Productive
Ramadan:
•Having suhoor as close as possible to Fajr
ensures that you have the right amount of energy to
keep you going the rest of the day.
•Staying awake after Fajr means that youre
benefitting from the dua of Prophet Muhammad (Peace
be upon him) in which he said: “O Allah, bless my
Ummah in its early hours” and you are getting more
work done compared to those who sleep till Dhuhr (or
Asr)!
30 Tips for a Guilt-Free Ramadan!
If you scored low in the above quiz, its time to reassess
your productivity and your time management during
Ramadan. Were less than 20 days away from Eid! Lets
make most of the remaining time we have.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_12">What Level Are You On?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_12">What Level Are You On?
As were approaching mid-Ramadan, we need to assess
ourselves in terms of Spiritual Productivity, Physical
Productivity, and Social Productivity.
Usually people can be divided into 3 categories around
this time:
Category 1: Those who started well and continue to do
well. These are the power-starters and those who push
themselves each and every day to make the most of
Ramadan!
Category 2: Those who started well, but slowly, start
to slip in their good deeds. These are the people who
had an amazing strong start, but soon they relaxed and
next thing they know their schedules have gone hay-
wire.
Category 3: Those who had a bad start and they are
not sure what they can do to catch up.
For those in Category 1 - may Allah (Subhanahu Wa
Taala) keep you steadfast! Keep up the good work and
never ever let go! It is as narrated in the hadith that
Allah loves good deeds that are done consistently.
For those in Category 2 - dont panic! Assess what
needs to change in your life so you can get back on
track and set yourself a target to do better in the next
10 days. Dont give up hope; the best part of this
month is yet to come InshaAllah!
For those in Category 3 - TODAY you must change! Get
up now, make wudu, pray 2 rakah to Allah Subhanahu
Wa Taala and ask Him to help you make the most of
Ramadan. If you continue as you are, come end of
Ramadan and youll face regret and, by that time, itll be
too late and youll have no one to blame but yourself.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_13">Dont Feel Like Being Productive?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_13">One of the biggest plagues of productivity is inconsis-
tency. If youve been finding it hard lately to pick your
copy of Quran and read that one Juz, or to stand up for
another 8 to 20 rakaahs for Taraweeh after Isha, or any
other good deed you used to do at the beginning of
Ramadan before dropping it, then we have a simple and
practical tip for you:
JUST GET UP and DO IT!
Take one small step towards the good deed and youll
be a mile off before you know it, InshaAllah. Just pick
up that Quran and read it. Just stand up and pray those
2 rakahs, then the next one, and the next one. Just
drive to that local charity group and volunteer your
time so you are surrounded by other people doing good
deeds.
Once you get into motion, your heart and mind will
follow. You just have to make that first step!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_14">Miss That Feeling?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_14">Once youre able to get over the ‘physical barrier doing
the good deed, its time to get over the mental barrier.
Ask yourself:
• Was it really that bad once Ive done [the good
deed] again and took the
first step?
• What was stopping me before?
• How can I avoid this feeling of not ‘feeling like
doing these good deeds
from time to time?
Were not going to answer these questions for you: we
want you to answer them. You may miss that feeling
you had at the beginning of Ramadan, yet you
shouldnt get hung-up with the thought that you just
dont want to do it.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_15">Have You Hit The Halfway Mark?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_15">Here are answers to a few frequently asked questions:
Q. How can you tell that youre physically tired vs.
simply being lazy?
A. Its easy for our laziness to be masked as physical
tiredness. We would stand at Taraweeh and our legs
would be shaking or reciting Quran and our eyelids
would be drooping, but the moment we go out of the
mosque or close the Quran, suddenly were feeling very
energetic! We have to be careful of this, catch ourselves
and rebuke it when we find out were not tired, but
simply being lazy.
Try to find the root cause for this laziness; is it lack of
sincerity? Low eman? A sin youve committed thats
preventing you from enjoying the good deed? Make dua
that Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala removes such laziness
from you. You dont want it to ruin your Ramadan.
However, if your body is genuinely aching and you
havent slept properly for days, then youre physically
tired and should get some urgent rest.
Q. How can one get over the mental thought “let me
just skip this good deed this time, Ill do it later?”
A. “Tasweef” – the Arabic word for delaying doing things
– is a common trick of Shaytaan. In fact it is one of his
one of his best tricks yet. It sounds so good to delay a
good deed until the ‘perfect time arrives; BUT the
perfect time will never come. The perfect time is NOW!
Also remember that each day of Ramadan that goes by
without you doing as many good deeds as you can is a
day thats gone forever, and youll never see it again till
the Day of Judgment. So how do you want to see your
Ramadan days on the Day of Judgment? Full of good
deeds or with empty slots because you kept ‘skipping
good deeds?
If youve come halfway through this blessed month,
dont let the good deeds slip; instead, invest in the few
days which remain.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_16">Success Only Comes From Allah</string>
    <string name="quote_description_16">On this very day, over 1400 years ago, the great battle
of Badr took place. We all know its story and how Allah
Subhanahu Wa Taala granted victory to Prophet
Muhammad (peace and blessings be upon him) and his
Companions (may Allah be pleased with them) on that
day. But what lessons can we learn from this battle
that is relevant to our productivity? Heres one:
After the battle was won, Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala
revealed the following verse: “And Allah has already
made you victorious at Badr, when you were a weak
little force. So fear Allah much that you may be grate-
ful” (Surat Aal-Imran; 3:123).
This was a reminder to the Muslims that any success or
victory is from Allah and Allah alone. They shouldnt be
arrogant and forget the source of their success. Some-
times when youre super productive and you achieve a
great deal in a day, its easy to assume that your
success comes from your skills or knowledge; but thats
not how a Muslim thinks. A Muslim firmly believes in
the verse that “And my success is not but through
Allah. Upon him I have relied, and to Him I return” (Surat
Hud; 11:88).
Finally, on this special day, make dua for our oppressed
brothers and sisters in many parts of the world. They
are having a difficult Ramadan and the least we can do
is make dua for them. We ask Allah (Subhanahu Wa
Taala) with His Might and Power, the One Who granted
His Prophet victory on the day of Badr to grant our
brothers and sisters victory over their oppressors and all
those who wrong them. Ameen!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_17">Whats Your Ideal Ramadan Day?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_17">The last 10 nights of Ramadan will begin soon. This is
the time well need to pull together all our energies and
all our productivity techniques to make sure we invest
in every moment of these last 10 nights to the best of
our ability.
You are invited to download the Ramadan Taskinator
today and start planning your last 10 days hour by
hour. Ask yourself, ”If I knew which night amongst the
10 nights is Laylut-Qadr (Night of Power), how would I
spend that night?” Then replicate that ‘ideal night
throughout the 10 nights or at least in the odd nights.
May the most productive amongst you gain the highest
rewards in these last nights and the reward of
Laylatul-Qadr! Ameen.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_18">Are You Like The Old Man In Salah?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_18">Two years ago, I prayed Taraweeh next to a very old
man. I noticed that he struggled to get up or stand on
his feet (he was shaking from weakness), but he stood
up for the entire Isha and Taraweeh prayers. Someone
might have told him to sit down and relax, but you
could tell from his determination at every rakah that he
wanted to stand up for Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala
during Ramadan and didnt want to sit down.
The old man reminded me that sometimes the measure
of how much you love someone is how much effort
youre willing to put in for them. If we truly love Allah
Subhanahu Wa Taala, shouldnt all of us put that extra
bit of effort for Him?
Think of one area or one activity where you show Allah
Subhanahu Wa Taala that youre putting that extra bit
of effort for Him. It could be waking up for Tahajjud or
praying those extra sunnah prayers or going out to feed
people.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_19">Busy In The Last 10 Nights?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_19">If we are to think of our purpose in life and our ultimate
destination, Jannah, the answer becomes very easy:
sacrifice your days work for 10 days so you can focus
on night worship. However, not everyone can do so.
So what can you do? Heres some advice:
• Employ good task and time management to be
able to balance between work and worship. Check out
the Ramadan Taskinator.
• Plan your day hour by hour and see which slots
you need to be at work, which slots you need to be at
the mosque, and what to do with the slots in between
to maximize your energy/time. (e.g. power naps, light
iftaar, etc.)
• Be ruthless in your time discipline and make
sure that no minute is wasted. Otherwise itll have a
knock on effect on the rest of your day. Dont be com-
placent about time-wasting activities, and really get
yourself on ‘high-alert mode.
Follow the above discipline like clockwork for at least
the last 10 nights and you should be fine, InshaAllah</string>

    <string name="quote_title_20">Natural Ways To Stay Awake</string>
    <string name="quote_description_20">For people who are busy working during the day, it can
be an extreme challenge to make the most of the last
10 nights for ibadah, and some may even resort to
unnatural ways of staying awake, including consuming
large amount of caffeine, which can be detrimental to
ones health.
Here are natural ways of staying awake at night
InshaAllah.
• Nap: Master short bursts of power naps. These
can range from 20 to 40 minutes, up to a maximum of
90 minutes. They are extremely powerful to keep you
awake and going for at least 3-4 hours after the nap.
Whenever youre tired and see a window of opportunity
to take a quick nap - do so. This will help keep you
going InshaAllah.
• Food: What we eat affects whether we can
stay up or sleep. The more we eat at iftaar/suhoor, the
more well feel sleepy. Eat light and healthier for these
10 nights and youll be able to observe the long night
prayers easily InshaAllah.
30 Tips for a Guilt-Free Ramadan!
• Make dua that Allah blesses you with energy, blesses
your sleep, and blesses your time so that you can make the
most of these blessed nights and reach maximum productiv-
ity through them, InshaAllah.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_21">What Will Be Your ONE SPECIAL Good Deed?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_21">What is the ONE special good deed that youd want to
remember your Ramadan with this year so you have no
regrets by the end of it? Something youve never done
before, something youve pushed yourself beyond your
means and out of your comfort zone to achieve!?
Here are some ideas:
• Go on a full 10-day itikaaf (or less perhaps if
this is your first time or if commitments dont permit)
• Take out your wallet and give the largest ONE
donation youve ever given in your life to a charitable
cause.
• Forgive that ONE person you said youd never
ever forgive.
• Get to know a poor family and vow to sponsor
them as long as you live.
• Arrange an Iftar at an orphanage
• Donate an important piece of asset you have
(e.g. land/property/farm) to Allah (Subhanahu Wa Taala)
in the form of Waqf (endowment).
Make this Ramadan truly memorable for your soul by
doing something extraordinary this Ramadan! Think
about it and take action!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_22">What Will Be Your ONE Good Deed (Part 2)?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_22">Today, think of the ONE good deed that you promise
yourself to continue doing after Ramadan. Which one
will it be?
Will it be praying Tahajjud every night from now on?
Will it be fasting every Monday and Thursday or at least
3 days of the month each month?
Will it be praying in the mosque for every single Salah?
Will it be reading one juz of Quran each day?
Will it be continually giving charity at least once a
week?
What will it be for you?
Remember, “the most beloved deed to Allahs is the
most regular and constant even though it were little”
[Bukhari].
These good deeds should be a part and parcel of your
life well after Ramadan – so pick one and write it down
and after Ramadan. Check yourself to ensure you
consistently perform this good deed.
The ProductiveMuslim Habitator is an excellent tool to
help you with this, InshaAllah!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_23">Are You Tired But Happy? :)</string>
    <string name="quote_description_23">If youve been keeping up with a productive Ramadan,
doing your best to balance between spiritual, social and
physical productivity, youll probably be a bit tired by
now.
But honestly, arent you happy that youre having a
Productive Ramadan and hopeful that Allah Subhanahu
Wa Taala will accept it? Imagine if you slept all day
during Ramadan and stayed all up night having fun
with friends and watching movies. Would you be as
happy?
Our happiness and sadness is connected to how close
we are with Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala. As human
beings, we inherently feel happy when we worship
Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala no matter how tired we get.
Similarly were ‘programmed to feel sadness when
were far from Allah, no matter how relaxed we are.
So if youre feeling a bit tired and drained these days,
feel happy that youre doing your best, smile, and ask
Allah to help you continue on His path!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_24">A One-to-One With Your Heart</string>
    <string name="quote_description_24">If youre standing in prayer in these last few days of
Ramadan doing your best to ‘feel closer to Allah Subha-
nahu Wa Taala yet somehow feeling distanced; if youre
wondering why those around you are all crying like
babies whilst youre completely emotionless; if you
wish you could be of those with soft hearts and tearful
eyes in Ramadan, but it doesnt seem to happen, and
you fail to reach that level in your spiritual worship –
then its time to have a serious one-to-one conversa-
tion with your heart.
Ask your heart: why is it so cold? Why do the Words of
its Creator have no effect or impact on it at all? Is it that
arrogant that it doesnt need its Lord?!
Why is it so hard? Why are no emotions expressed for
either fear or joy of being with its Creator? Why is it a
hypocrite? Itll cry watching a movie when it knows its
not real but will not cry when it hears the truth about
its ultimate destination?!
Keep digging deeper until you find the answer. Get your
heart to break in front of Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala
this Ramadan. Theres no sweeter feeling than a
sincere heart that cries out to Allah. Dont let Ramadan
go without having cried even once in front of your Lord
InshaAllah</string>

    <string name="quote_title_25">A Practical Way To Scrub Your Heart Clean!</string>
    <string name="quote_description_25">The Messenger of Allah (Peace be upon him) said:
"There is a polish for everything that takes away rust;
and the polish for the heart is remembrance of God"
[Bukhari].
The Messenger of Allah (Peace be upon him) said,
“Renew your faith!” It was said, “O Messenger of Allah,
how do we renew our faith?” He (Peace be upon him)
replied, “By saying la ilaha illa Allah (‘There is no god
but God) a lot” [Ahmad and Hakim].
So there you have it: two simple prescriptions to soften
your heart, remove the rust from it and feel closer to
Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala, especially in these last few
days of Ramadan.
Try it today. Say "La ilaha illa Allah" repeatedly - when
driving, sitting at your computer, cooking, or playing
with your child – just say it and keep saying it!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_26">Will You Continue On This Journey?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_26">A feeling of ‘sadness clouds our hearts around this
time each year. We wonder if well ever continue being
this spiritual and close to Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala.
Past experience has shown that we always fail to keep
up after Ramadan, so what can we do to ensure the
journey doesnt end here?
Heres a video on this topic in which I share 6 tips with.
One of the big reasons why we ‘fall after Ramadan is
that we lose self-discipline. We have this false idea in
our mind that “Its Eid! Do whatever you want!” (Even
though we dont actually say this, our actions certainly
do!)
One of the best ways to fight this is to instill discipline
in your life from day 1 of Eid. From day 1 of Eid, make
sure you wake up early and stay up during those early
hours of the morning! Occupy these precious hours
with reading quietly, doing some housekeeping tasks,
or even taking your children to the park for a nice
picnic.
By this ONE simple act of waking up early (for Fajr at
least) and staying up in those early hours, youll be
instilling self-discipline in your life which will radiate in
the rest of your day/actions, InshaAllah. Also, by this
one simple act, youll be setting yourself up for a
productive and healthy post-Ramadan lifestyle thats
going to help you throughout the year, InshaAllah.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_27">Your Last Productive Act</string>
    <string name="quote_description_27">To end this Ramadan feeling satisfied, what is the last
productive thing you should do this Ramadan? You
dont need to think about it. Prophet Muhammad (peace
and blessings be upon him) already told us! Its paying
zakat-al-fitr!
If you can, try to give this zakat in person this Ramadan
instead of doing it via a charitable organization.
Its very easy. All you have to do is follow these 3 steps:
• Go buy 3KG of rice/dates on behalf of yourself
+ each of your family
members whom you support.
• Find a needy Muslim person/family in your
local area.
• Deliver! (If you can deliver secretly by leaving it
at their doorstep, it
would be even better InshaAllah).
Although its ‘easier and less of a ‘hassle to do it via a
charity organization or online these days, its a different
feeling when you do it physically and deliver it by hand.
May Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala accept all your good
deeds in these last blessed nights!</string>

    <string name="quote_title_28">Ramadan Went By So Fast?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_28">If you feel Ramadan went by so fast this year, its
either because you had such an amazing productive
Ramadan that time flew by fast and you didnt feel it,
OR you were so busy that you didnt notice Ramadan at
all except in these last few days.
If you had a ProductiveRamadan, a heartfelt congratula-
tions from the ProductiveMuslim team – we pray that
Allah Subhanahu Wa Taala accepts your deeds and
grants you many more productive Ramadans in years to
come.
If, unfortunately, you didnt make the most of Ramadan
and you had a truly unproductive one, do not despair.
All you need now is to sincerely face Allah Subhanahu
Wa Taala in these last few hours before Ramadan ends
and seek repentance from Him for letting this Ramadan
slip by you without focusing on it. The worst thing you
can do now is to lose hope in Allah Subhanahu Wa
Taalas mercy. Repent, give yourself hope, and start
putting concrete action steps to make the most of next
years Ramadan, InshaAllah.</string>

    <string name="quote_title_29">How will you be after Ramadan?</string>
    <string name="quote_description_29">I am going to guess what youre thinking today: youre
wondering (or rather youre doubtful) if youll continue
your productivity after Ramadan.
I wont lecture you on the importance of keeping up
your productivity (spiritually, physically, socially) after
Ramadan. Im sure youre receiving lots of reminders
from your local imam and scholars that are talking
about this. But Ill say this:
If, in any moment during the last 29 days, you felt the
sweetness of being a Muslim and you want that sweet-
ness to be with you till after Ramadan, then you must
continue being spiritually, physically, and socially
productive after Ramadan.
How? The formula is very simple: Have sincere inten-
tions and work hard.
I leave you with that thought today</string>

    <string name="quote_title_30">Eid Mubarak and Thank You!</string>
    <string name="quote_description_30">Well, this is it – the end of a long beautiful month – but
hopefully the start of a new productive life! ;)
The ProductiveMuslim team wishes you all a happy,
blessed and – of course – Productive Eid!</string>
</resources>